Little do you know
How I’m breaking while you fall asleep
I’m still haunted by the memory
Little do you know
I’m trying to pick myself from piece by piece
I need a little more time
Underneath it all I’m held captive by the hole inside
I’ve been holding back
For the fear that you might change your mind
I’m ready to forgive you but forgetting is a harder fight
Little do you know
I need a little more time
Away, away
I love you like you've never felt the pain, away
I promise you don’t have to be afraid, away
The love you see right here stays so lay your head on me
Little do you know
I know you’re hurt while I'm sound asleep
All my mistakes are solely drowning me
Little do you know
I’m trying to make it better piece by piece
I, I love you till the sun dies
Away, just wait
I love you like I've never felt the pain, just wait
I love you like I’ve never been afraid, just wait
Our love we see right here stays so lay your head on me
Away, away
I love you like you've never felt the pain, away
I promise you don’t have to be afraid, away
The love you see right here stays so lay your head on me
Lay your head on me
So lay your head on me
'Cause little do you know
I love you till the sun dies